<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<person>
	<FullName>Michael Schr&amp;ouml;der</FullName>
	<publication>
		<title>Classifying Event-Related Desynchronization in EEG, ECoG and MEG Signals</title>
		<year>2006</year>
		<authors>n. jeremy hill,thomas navin lal,thilo hinterberger,guido widman,christian erich elger,bernhard schölkopf,niels birbaumer</authors>
		<jconf>DAGM Symposium Symposium for Pattern Recognition</jconf>
		<label>706</label>
		<keyword>Brain Computer Interface;Clinical Application;Event Related Desynchronization;Independent Component Analysis;Machine Learning;Motor Imagery;Spatial Filtering;Common Spatial Pattern;</keyword>
		<organization>null</organization>
		<abstract>We present the results from three motor-imagery-based Brain-Computer Interface experiments. Brain signals were recorded from 8 untrained subjects using EEG, 4 using ECoG and 10 using MEG. In all cases, we aim to develop a system that could be used for fast, reliable preliminary screening in the clinical application of a BCI, so we aim to obtain the best possible</abstract>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Feature selection for high-dimensional industrial data</title>
		<year>2005</year>
		<authors>michael bensch,martin bogdan,wolfgang rosenstiel</authors>
		<jconf>The European Symposium on Artificial Neural Networks</jconf>
		<label>706</label>
		<keyword>Feature Selection;High Dimensionality;Quality Assurance;Quality Control;</keyword>
		<organization>null</organization>
		<abstract>In the semiconductor industry the number of circuits per chip is still drastically increasing. This fact and strong competition lead to the particular importance of quality control and quality assurance. As a result a vast amount of data is recorded during the fabrication process, which is very complex in structure and massively affected by noise. The evaluation of this data</abstract>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Towards the restoration of hand grasp function of quadriplegic patients based on an artificial neural net controller using peripheral nerve stimulation - an approach</title>
		<year>2003</year>
		<authors>martin bogdan,wolfgang rosenstiel</authors>
		<jconf>The European Symposium on Artificial Neural Networks</jconf>
		<label>706</label>
		<keyword>Artificial Neural Net;Artificial Neural Network;Central Nervous System;Control Strategy;Muscle Fatigue;Peripheral Nerve;Position Control;Peripheral Nerve Stimulation;Real Time;</keyword>
		<organization>null</organization>
		<abstract>We propose a closed loop strategy for the control of hand grasp movements for paralyzed patients which is based on an artificial neural network (ANN). For this goal an ANN controller applies functional neuroelectrical stimulation (FNS) to a peripheral nerve with the aim to ini- tiate axonal stimulation patterns similar to those generated by the central nervous system. In this</abstract>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>A brain computer interface with online feedback based on magnetoencephalography</title>
		<year>2005</year>
		<authors>thomas navin lal,n. jeremy hill,hubert preissl,thilo hinterberger,jürgen mellinger,martin bogdan,wolfgang rosenstiel,thomas hofmann,niels birbaumer,bernhard schölkopf</authors>
		<jconf>International Conference on Machine Learning</jconf>
		<label>706</label>
		<keyword>Brain Computer Interface;Electroencephalography;Healthy Subjects;Human Brain;Machine Learning;magnetoencephalography;Motor Imagery;Signal To Noise Ratio;brain computer in terface;Proof of Concept;</keyword>
		<organization>null</organization>
		<abstract>The aim of this paper is to show that machine learning techniques can be used to derive a classifying function for human brain signal data measured by magnetoencephalography (MEG), for the use in a brain computer in- terface (BCI). This is especially helpful for evaluating quickly whether a BCI approach based on electroencephalography, on which training may be slower due</abstract>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Reducing Calibration Time For Brain-Computer Interfaces: A Clustering Approach</title>
		<year>2006</year>
		<authors>matthias krauledat,benjamin blankertz,klaus-robert müller</authors>
		<jconf>Neural Information Processing Systems</jconf>
		<label>706</label>
		<keyword>Brain Computer Interface;Machine Learning;</keyword>
		<organization>null</organization>
		<abstract>Up to now even subjects that are experts in the use of machine learning based BCI systems still have to undergo a calibration session of about 20-30 min. From this data their (movement) intentions are so far infered. We now propose a new paradigm that allows to completely omit such calibration and instead transfer knowledge from prior sessions. To achieve</abstract>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Methods Towards Invasive Human Brain Computer Interfaces</title>
		<year>2004</year>
		<authors>thomas navin lal,thilo hinterberger,guido widman,n. jeremy hill,wolfgang rosenstiel,christian erich elger,bernhard schölkopf,niels birbaumer</authors>
		<jconf>Neural Information Processing Systems</jconf>
		<label>706</label>
		<keyword>Brain Computer Interface;Human Brain;Intracranial Eeg;Motor Cortex;Signal To Noise Ratio;Support Vector Machine;</keyword>
		<organization>null</organization>
		<abstract>During the last ten years there has been growing interest in the develop- ment of Brain Computer Interfaces (BCIs). The eld has mainly been driven by the needs of completely paralyzed patients to communicate. With a few exceptions, most human BCIs are based on extracranial elec- troencephalography (EEG). However, reported bit rates are still low. One reason for this is</abstract>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Region-Based Image Classification for Automatic Color Correction</title>
		<year>2003</year>
		<authors>clément fredembach,sabine süsstrunk</authors>
		<jconf>Color Imaging Conference</jconf>
		<label>707</label>
		<keyword>Color Correction;Image Classification;Image Features;</keyword>
		<organization>null</organization>
		<abstract>This work presents a framework for image classification based on region information. The main application of this framework is for automatic color correction of real-scene images. Class specific color correction is already imple- mented in some systems, but image classification usually relies on global image features only. Our region-based ap- proach shows a significant improvement over previously achieved classification for</abstract>
	</publication>
	<publication>
		<title>Eigenregions for Image Classification</title>
		<year>2004</year>
		<authors>clément fredembach,sabine süsstrunk</authors>
		<jconf>IEEE Transactions on Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence</jconf>
		<label>707</label>
		<keyword>Geometric Feature;Image Classification;Image Features;Natural Images;Principal Component Analysis;Regional Analysis;</keyword>
		<organization>null</organization>
		<abstract>For certain databases and classification tasks, analyzing images based on region features instead of image features results in more accurate classifications. We introduce eigenregions, which are geometrical features that encompass area, location and shape properties of an image region, even if the region is spatially incoherent. Eigenregions are calculated using principal component analysis (PCA). On a database of 77'000 dierent</abstract>
	</publication>
</person>
